{
  "results": [{
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "How many jobs in Technology were held by women in 2021?",
      "correct_answer": "25%",
      "incorrect_answers": ["20%", "40%", "35%"]
  }, {
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "How many tech startups have at least one woman on the board of directors?",
      "correct_answer": "37%",
      "incorrect_answers": ["42%", "32%", "28%"]
  }, {
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which percentaje of startups across the world were founded by women?",
      "correct_answer": "20%",
      "incorrect_answers": ["15%", "10%", "25%"]
  }, {
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Who was the World's First Computer Programmer?",
      "correct_answer": "Ada Lovelace",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Ángela Ruiz Robles", "Betty Snyder Holberton", "Gladys Mae West"]
  }, {
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which country has the largest population of female developers?",
      "correct_answer": "India",
      "incorrect_answers": ["China", "Italy;", "United States"]
  }, {
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is known as one of the famous women in technology who inspired Steve Jobs creation of the first Apple computer as, without her, the Apple desktop environment may not look the way it does today?",
      "correct_answer": "Adele Goldberg",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Mary Wilkes", "Annie Easley", "Grace Hopper"]
  }, {
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "How many of Sillicon Valley executives are women?",
      "correct_answer": "11%",
      "incorrect_answers": ["8%", "15%", "18%"]
  }, {
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Select the city with the largest number of tech startups founded by women",
      "correct_answer": "Chicago",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Silicon Valley", "Los Angeles", "London"]
  }, {
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who was the first woman in being IBM CEO (from 2012-2020)?",
      "correct_answer": "Ginni Rometty",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Millie Hughes", "Gina Bianchini", "Melanie Perkins"]
  }, {
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Who was the first woman engineer in Spain in 1929?",
      "correct_answer": "Pilar Careaga",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Ana María Prieto", "Ángela Ruiz Robles", "Evelyn Berezin"]
  }, {
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who was Spain first woman Computer Programmer?",
      "correct_answer": "Ana María Prieto",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Ángela Ruiz Robles", "Pilar Careaga", "Evelyn Berezin"]
  }, {
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who invented the first English-like data processing language – which sparked the development of COBOL?",
      "correct_answer": "Grace Hopper",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Radia Perlman", "Ada Lovelace", "Mary Kenneth Keller"]
  }, {
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who was the first woman to receive a PhD in Computer Science?",
      "correct_answer": "Sister Mary Kenneth Keller",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Radia Perlman", "Ada Lovelace", "Grace Hopper"]
  }, {
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Who was the woman that invented online dating?",
      "correct_answer": "Joan Ball",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Adele Goldberg", "Radia Perlman", "Grace Hopper"]
  }, {
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which was the first international online women Hackaton?",
      "correct_answer": "FemHack",
      "incorrect_answers": ["WomenUnitedHack", "WomenHack", "GirlsHack"]
  }, {
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who invented the 'secret communication system', the idea that eventually inspired Wi-Fi, PS and Bluetooth technology commonly used today?",
      "correct_answer": "Hedy Lamarr",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Annie Easley", "Grace Hopper", "Radia Perlman"]
  }, {
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who was nicknamed “Mother of the Internet” due to invention of the algorithm behind the Spanning Tree Protocol (STP), that was instrumental in making today's internet possible?",
      "correct_answer": "Radia Perlman",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Grace Hopper", "Hedy Lamarr", "Adele Goldberg"]
  }, {
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who invented the Data Secretary, the first electronic word processor?",
      "correct_answer": "Evelyn Berezin",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Hedy Lamarr", "Grace Hopper", "Adele Goldberg"]
  }, {
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which is the ratio of men to women in software engineering?",
      "correct_answer": "5:1",
      "incorrect_answers": ["5:2", "5:3", "5:4"]
  }, {
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which are the tech companies that hire most women?",
      "correct_answer": "Companies with less than 1000 employees",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Companies with 1000-1500 employees", "Companies with 1500-2000 employees", "Companies with more than 2000 employees"]
  }]
}